[{"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小宇在阳阳的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小宇", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小宇.svg"}, {"name": "阳阳", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/阳阳.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，阳阳在淘淘的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "阳阳", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/阳阳.svg"}, {"name": "淘淘", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/淘淘.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小明在小冬的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小冬", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小冬.svg"}, {"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小明在小宇的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小宇", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小宇.svg"}, {"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，淘淘在小凡的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小凡", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小凡.svg"}, {"name": "淘淘", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/淘淘.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，淘淘在小明的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}, {"name": "淘淘", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/淘淘.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小明在小宇的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}, {"name": "小宇", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小宇.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小明在阳阳的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}, {"name": "阳阳", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/阳阳.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，阳阳在淘淘的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "淘淘", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/淘淘.svg"}, {"name": "阳阳", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/阳阳.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小宇在小凡的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小凡", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小凡.svg"}, {"name": "小宇", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小宇.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，阳阳在小凡的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小凡", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小凡.svg"}, {"name": "阳阳", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/阳阳.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小凡在小明的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}, {"name": "小凡", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小凡.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小冬在小明的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}, {"name": "小冬", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小冬.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小冬在小宇的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小冬", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小冬.svg"}, {"name": "小宇", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小宇.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小凡在小冬的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小凡", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小凡.svg"}, {"name": "小冬", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小冬.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小凡在小宇的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小凡", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小凡.svg"}, {"name": "小宇", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小宇.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小冬在淘淘的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "淘淘", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/淘淘.svg"}, {"name": "小冬", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小冬.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小明在小冬的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}, {"name": "小冬", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小冬.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小宇在小冬的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小冬", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小冬.svg"}, {"name": "小宇", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小宇.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，阳阳在小明的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}, {"name": "阳阳", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/阳阳.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，阳阳在小凡的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "阳阳", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/阳阳.svg"}, {"name": "小凡", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小凡.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，小明在淘淘的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "淘淘", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/淘淘.svg"}, {"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["右"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，淘淘在小明的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "淘淘", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/淘淘.svg"}, {"name": "小明", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小明.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选一选，淘淘在小凡的哪边？", "personList": [{"name": "淘淘", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/儿童/淘淘.svg"}, {"name": "小凡", "src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_back/大人/小凡.svg"}], "options": ["左", "右"], "type": "pos-sequence-select6"}], "answers": ["左"], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-3-02"}]